

SIRET FRANK Full-Stack developer

- Av. Federico Rey #4 Santiago de Cuba
- **&** (+53) 551 218 66

SOCIAL

- in @frank-siret
- @FrankSiret
- @FrankSiret

PROFILE

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science & Full Stack Developer. With good skills in mathematics, algorithms, and programming languages. I have several years of experience and achievements in the labor field. I like to improve my skills and I always push myself the most.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIECE

Universidad de Oriente - Cuba

2014 - 2019

Graduated with Gold Title and Scientific Merit Award.

Second best students from the 2019 class.

Several scientific events related to Computer Science.

Involved for 5 years in the ICPC Competitive Programming. See

More

Degree Thesis in the field of Information Retrieval.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

From 2021 | People Walking

Designed and developed UI/UX for a centralized backup center application for Ancert (http://www.ancert.com) the National Certification Agency or Notary of Spain.

Support junior developer boot camps on React JS and helped improve their knowledge in the library.

Developed reusable components that help the team to finish Backup Center project earlier than planned.

Fully remote work, completing assigned tasks on time, meeting customer requirements and working under pressure.

Daily work progress reports following the workflow set by the team using Beanstalk source version control software and Jira software development Tool.

Technologies used

React JS

Typescript

Bootstrap 4

Spring Boot (with JHipster)

PostgreSQL

Computer Science Professor

From 2019 | Universidad de Oriente

Teaches classes of Logic Math, Data Structures, and Artificial Inteligence. Stands as Assistant Director of the International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) at the University.

Won the annual CITMA Award for Young Researchers.

Freelance Full-Stack Developer

From 2020 to 2021 | Freelance

Designed and developed the website https://www.reysis.com for a small business in Cuba.

Guided digital marketing strategy for positioning the business on the web.

Developed frontend user interface.

Worked in a team of two members using agile methodologies (XP). Conducted meetings with the client and designed application architecture.

Technologies used

React

Bootstrap 4

API Platform

Swagger

MySQL

C++ Developer

From 2017 to 2021 | Centro de Biofísica Médica

Contributed to designed and developed the medical imaging software **Imagis**.

Support junior developer on C++ and helped improve their knowledge in the language.

Worked in more than 10 features such as design report management

SKILLS

- Html
- Css
- Sass
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Spring Boot
- C/C++
- Java

See More

worked in more than to reattares sach as acsign, report management, transmission, visualization, and image segmentation.

Technologies used

C++

Java

VTK

ITK

DCMTK

Qt Framework

Lucene

Information Retrieval

CERTIFICATES

React Certificate

Dec 2020 | HackerRank

Provide knowledge and skills required to become a successful web and mobile application developer.

Problem Solving Certificate

Nov 2020 | HackerRank

Standardized assessment to help developers prove their coding skills.

LANGUAGES

• Spanish • English

INTERESTS

Ё

7

Music Cofee

Travel

Read



Origami